<cues>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>2.12</start>
    <end>2.25</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; OK, so we&#8217;re on.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker &amp; Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>2.26</start>
    <end>27.03</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; OK, well my name is Mary Parker and right now I live in Fayetteville, Arkansas, which is where I&#8217;m from, generally. I&#8217;m a member of the Grinnell College class of 2006.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Great. So, we have some questions.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Go ahead with the questions, that&#8217;s fine.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; What were your first memories of Grinnell?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>27.04</start>
    <end>60.19</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Well I never prospied here, and I never came to see it before I showed up, so I just rolled into town. I remember being really freaked out that Mom and I could not find any exit signs that said anything about Grinnell. No &#8220;Grinnell 20 miles&#8221; whatever until &#8220;Grinnell 6 miles&#8221; by the rest area and then we&#8217;re thinking, &#8220;OK, here we go, we&#8217;re actually gonna find it.&#8221; So it was, a little strange at first &#8216;cause I thought, &#8220;You&#8217;re a college town, surely there&#8217;s a sign.&#8221; No sign.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>60.2</start>
    <end>90.11</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; But, I remember really liking it as we came into town. It's different from where I live, it&#8217;s more town-y less city-y. So, I just thought it was cute. I really liked the redbrick buildings and all the move-in people were super friendly and then Mom didn&#8217;t want to leave and she wanted to come here and go to college here, despite the fact that she&#8217;s been to college, she&#8217;s got a master&#8217;s degree and everything.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs &amp; Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>90.12</start>
    <end>103.22</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Great, what were your best memories of your time at Grinnell College?&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Wow.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; I know, it&#8217;s kind of a big one.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>103.23</start>
    <end>139.11</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; I don&#8217;t know. There&#8217;s a lot of really good memories, and a lot of kind silly memories. I remember, one time going to watch the India Pakistan cricket match on the big screen in ARH. It was obviously the middle of the night &#8216;cause it was played on the other side of the world, so we slept for a long time on the couches in the lounge area and then we got up to watch the rest of the game and it was winter and it was really really icy outside and so it was early in the morning when we finished watching the game.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>139.12</start>
    <end>174.17</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; We were walking back across and there was this huge patch of ice by the train tracks and I slipped and I just fell right over and I couldn&#8217;t stop laughing about it. Then I got up and I fell over again immediately and I couldn&#8217;t stop laughing and everybody else was like, &#8220;What are you doing? Just get up.&#8221; but I was like, &#8220;This is hilarious. Been up too late watchin&#8217; cricket. Now, I can&#8217;t stop falling on the ice." It was just one of those really silly moments. It was fun.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>174.18</start>
    <end>182.23</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Yeah. What kind of, I guess, going back, why did you decide to come to Grinnell?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>182.24</start>
    <end>226.09</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; I used to have this really good story about how I was just flipping through my college book and it fell open to the Grinnell page and I thought, &#8220;Oh, well I&#8217;ll apply there, sure why not?&#8221; And then I told my mother this story, and she was like, &#8220;Yeah, I kinda creased the book so it would fall open to that page.&#8221; &#8216;Cause she&#8217;d been looking through that book too and I guess she really liked the look of Grinnell. It was kind of a choice for me between here and a sort of similar college in Maryland called St. Mary&#8217;s and then UNC Chapel Hill, I thought about going there but Grinnell seemed like the best bet. And, they gave really good scholarship money and good support and it seemed like they had a lot of interesting things going on for the middle of Iowa.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs &amp; Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>226.1</start>
    <end>243.12</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Yeah, definitely.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; So here I was. And they called me a lot of times.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Really?&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Yeah, yeah they called me a lot. It was kind of flattering. It was nice.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs &amp; Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>243.13</start>
    <end>257.29</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; How has Grinnell changed since you were a student? I know it wasn&#8217;t that long ago, but.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Oh no, it&#8217;s still changed. The JRC, do you call it the Joe?&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Usually the JRC.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; I know you&#8217;re supposed to call it the Joe.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs &amp; Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>258.0</start>
    <end>266.23</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Some people call it the Joe, some people call it the &#8220;jerk.&#8221;&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Oh, the guy wanted it to be called the Joe.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Oh really? Most people just say the JRC.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>266.24</start>
    <end>330.29</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; I figured. Yeah, that wasn&#8217;t there. It was just being built. There was a lot of construction when I was here &#8216;cause the first year, the East campus dorms weren&#8217;t finished so, I know, it&#8217;s crazy for you but for me they were just brand new and we were all like, "What is goin-?" It looked like a big ocean liner, &#8216;cause it was just a frame and then the lights, and they&#8217;d keep us up all night. &#8216;Cause I lived in Younker my first year and my room faced Mac Field so, just lights into the window all night long, but yeah we would sneak into the construction site illegally. I was so afraid I was going to get caught and expelled, I only did it once. It was pretty cool, in the middle of the night, walking around the construction site, little thrill of danger. Can&#8217;t kick me out now. Yeah, those weren&#8217;t there until my second year I guess, and even then D wasn&#8217;t finished, whatever it&#8217;s.. Rose?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs &amp; Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>331.0</start>
    <end>343.15</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Rathje.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; What&#8217;s it called?&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Rathje.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Rathje?&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Yeah, they named them-&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; I don&#8217;t think it had a name.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; I don&#8217;t think it had a name for a while &#8216;cause they couldn&#8217;t find a donor.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; We just called it Hall D.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Yeah, now it&#8217;s Rathje.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker &amp; Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>343.16</start>
    <end>382.21</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Good to know. And, the science center wasn&#8217;t all fancy. When I started here, instead of this there was Darby gym and the little, it was just this little house where the medical office, the nurse&#8217;s office thing and Stonewall were, and then they tore those down.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Wow, and where was the house?&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Just next to Darby. Yeah, kind of where that parking lot is now. That parking lot that you can&#8217;t actually park in, as I discovered yesterday.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs &amp; Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>382.22</start>
    <end>417.17</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; What, can you describe something that is no longer available on campus, but that was meaningful to you during your time here?&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Well, there&#8217;s Darby. That was meaningful, just &#8216;cause, it was old and it was neat and it was unique, pretty much, in the country because of the way it was constructed. Because of WWII, there not being enough steel I guess, it was built out of wood.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Really?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>417.18</start>
    <end>441.03</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Yeah, the supports and the ceiling were all built out of wood and we all loved it. It was this crazy old place. We didn&#8217;t think they'd ever tear it down and then they did, and we were sad about that. In terms of programs, I don&#8217;t really know. When I was here I was in the Buddies program. I helped run the Buddies program and Exco, but I think both of those are still going.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs &amp; Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>441.04</start>
    <end>465.24</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Yeah.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Which is great.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; And the buddies program was with the elementary school?&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; When I was leaving we integrated it with Big Brothers Big Sisters, so it had some more official cache. Other than that I don&#8217;t know what there was. It seems like they just keep adding programs, not too much taking them away.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; That&#8217;s really interesting about Darby, though.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker &amp; Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>465.25</start>
    <end>490.17</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; There was the Forum. We had a pool table in the Forum, in the middle room and on the outsides there were bean bag rooms. It&#8217;s not really an essential service, but.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; I&#8217;ve heard stories about the Forum, yeah.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; It was a good place. I used to work in the Grill so.. It was attached to the Forum. But I&#8217;m glad they didn&#8217;t tear it down.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; What was the Grill like?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>490.18</start>
    <end>529.15</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; It was cool. When I started we had Northern express and Southern express, that were these little like convenience stores where you could go in and get a meal equivalency of food or buy some food, and there was obviously one on each thing and we called them Nexpress and Sexpress because we&#8217;re silly. And then, eventually they shut them down and moved them into the room that had had the pool stuff in it. Well, they tried to move it into the main part of the Grill, so it looked like a gas station. We were all really angry and the professors were so angry.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs &amp; Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>529.16</start>
    <end>534.28</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Really?&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; They were so grumpy.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Because would they often eat there?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>534.29</start>
    <end>560.2</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Yeah, because they&#8217;d go and they&#8217;d take people to get tea or coffee or a snack or whatever, like interview people. Sometimes we&#8217;d have class in there, I remember my second year before they moved all the stuff into the pool room there were tables in there and we had class in there a few times with one of my seminars. And, &#8216;cause we got bored. It was in the afternoon and we all needed coffee.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>560.21</start>
    <end>585.24</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Sometimes we&#8217;d go there or Saint&#8217;s Rest and yeah, it just looked like a gas station convenience store and they had all these problems with people stealing stuff because they were angry and the professors complained, so eventually they moved all of that stuff up into the room that&#8217;d had the pool table in it and they instituted the grab &#8216;n gos where Nexpress used to be. I don&#8217;t know if it&#8217;s still up there.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>585.25</start>
    <end>588.15</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; There is outtakes now.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>588.16</start>
    <end>626.02</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Right, &#8216;cause you have it all centralized. Well, it was up in Cowles, in the little room off the side of what used to be the dining hall, which I guess is now apartments? Yeah, I worked there too. It was fun, baggin' up lunches. I liked it, I liked working in the dining hall. It was good. I had a pretty sweet deal my second year, &#8216;cause I worked, pretty much exclusively breakfast shifts and pretty much exclusively as the card checker so I had to get up early but it was totally worth it. But I started, definitely, in the back on the plate line. Good old Lyle.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>626.03</start>
    <end>627.03</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; We&#8217;ve all been there.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>627.04</start>
    <end>654.2</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Yes we have. Yes we have, which is a good thing about Grinnell, I think, that a lot of people work in dining services so it&#8217;s less degrading than it could be. &#8216;Cause when you work in dining services people have a tendency to pretend you&#8217;re invisible, even if they know you pretty well. So, it&#8217;s nice that lots of people work there.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs &amp; Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>654.21</start>
    <end>677.08</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Describe your favorite academic experience or class, like what was your major?&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; I doubled in English and French.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Oh, I&#8217;m a French major.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Excellent! Well, I really recommend that you do the program that they will tell you about next year where you spend the year teaching in France.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; I&#8217;ve heard about that.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>677.09</start>
    <end>715.16</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; You should do it. I did it and it was awesome. I can&#8217;t really think of too many classes that I didn&#8217;t really like. Probably one of my favorite classes though was the seminar on the Romantics with Erik Simpson because he&#8217;s so great and the Romantics are just one of my favorite periods in literature &#8216;cause they&#8217;re so dramatic about everything. It just makes me laugh so much. And the writing is good, but it&#8217;s fun to read &#8216;cause it&#8217;s so dramatic. Lord Byron. Oh, crazy Lord Byron, but we always had such good discussions in that class, it was really just really cozy.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>715.17</start>
    <end>751.12</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; I liked my seminar with Shuchi Kapila on Postcolonialism. &#8216;Cause I was a sophomore and I felt all special that they let me into this seminar, and that was the one where we would go for coffee in the forum or Saint&#8217;s Rest but it was just nice, &#8216;cause y&#8217;know even though I was a sophomore I felt like people let me talk and respected my opinion and we had some really good discussions on some really interesting topics that a lot of people don&#8217;t think about. It really helped me out later when I did my study abroad &#8216;cause I went to Southern India.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs &amp; Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>751.13</start>
    <end>777.07</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Wow, how was that?&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Wonderful, and I would go back in a heartbeat and I loved it. It was the best. I spent three and a half months there staying with a host family and studying Tamil and Indian religion and literature and politics, and then I spent about 5 or 6 weeks traveling around India.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Oh, that sounds great.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>777.08</start>
    <end>829.2</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Which was awesome. Even when I was sick and miserable, it was still awesome. I got to meet up with some people and just ate the best food ever and I saw all the sights that you could really ever wanna see. Except, I didn&#8217;t get to go to Kashmir &#8216;cause nobody really gets to go to Kashmir lately, especially if you are an American. So, but, I did get to see a whole lot of things that I would not have gotten to see if I had not gone to Grinnell I think, &#8216;cause there aren&#8217;t too many study abroad programs in India. I was dating an Indian guy at the time so, it was like &#8220;Oh, the experience, it&#8217;s interesting.&#8221; Plus, I&#8217;ve always been interested in India.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>829.21</start>
    <end>839.03</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Definitely. Cool. What was student and campus life like during your time at Grinnell?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>839.04</start>
    <end>881.2</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Pretty laid back. I mean, there was the usual row every now and again about, "Oh, self-governance is dying! It wasn&#8217;t like this when we were first years!" So I feel like that&#8217;s probably still going on. But, self governance was still alive most of the time. We got that campus bikes added to- South campus bikes. Yeah, that was when they started, and when they started they were all these ugly old things painted orange, spray-painted orange, and somebody took my bike a couple times claiming they thought it was a campus bike, even though my bike was red, and not obviously spray-painted orange. But, people would throw the campus bikes off the loggia.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>881.21</start>
    <end>910.18</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; And we had a couple of incidents of homophobic stuff, I guess, being written up on places. But, just one or two. I feel like that&#8217;s been going on lately from what I hear on plans, like homophobic and some racist stuff every now and again crops up but, it&#8217;s really hard to get away from that.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>910.19</start>
    <end>917.19</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Yeah. I would say once a year there&#8217;s probably a big- pretty big controversy.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker &amp; Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>917.2</start>
    <end>947.12</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Probably the biggest thing that ever happened when I was at Grinnell was, my first year and that was when we had all the suicides at once and it was really, just felt like the end of the world.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; How did that affect the campus atmosphere?&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Everybody just went around looking really quiet and sad and unhappy and the weather was also awful. We had hail the size of softballs.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Was this at the beginning of the year?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>947.13</start>
    <end>969.0</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; No, it was hell week. Spring semester hell week. So, everybody was already stressed out and they canceled a lot of finals eventually, but it was just. And everybody was so mad at the administration because we felt like they weren&#8217;t doing what they were supposed to, and they came up with the suicide contracts after that, and we were really mad about that, too.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>969.01</start>
    <end>969.23</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; What were those?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>969.24</start>
    <end>1027.2</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; If somebody goes to the therapist and expresses a will to kill themselves or to do harm to themselves they have to sign a contract that says they won&#8217;t. Which, if somebody&#8217;s gonna kill themselves they&#8217;re not gonna care about this piece of paper. But it was just, so.. I mean it&#8217;s a small place. You knew pretty much everybody on campus, or you knew somebody who knew them and one of the people that killed themselves lived in Younker in like, the room above my room. The other one was a friend of mine and he lived on the floor where I practically lived, 'cause I spent all my time there. And, the person who tried to kill herself was also a friend of mine. It was just. It was just terrible. You didn&#8217;t know if you were gonna wake up and hear that somebody else had tried to kill themselves or, and we never talked about it after that, really.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>1027.21</start>
    <end>1028.1</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Really?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>1028.11</start>
    <end>1058.22</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Yeah. I mean, after that week they had this big meeting and it was like, &#8220;If you&#8217;re grieving for these people, if you have some things to say come to this meeting,&#8221; and it felt like nobody was listening. They were like, &#8220;But we came up with a suicide contract,&#8221; we were like, &#8220;How does that help? What does that do?&#8221; It was just, really felt like the end of the world. And then... Well, it was just crazy.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>1058.23</start>
    <end>1090.17</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; The only other time that I really remember talking about it was senior year, in one of my seminars. We had this end-of-the-semester graduation party and we were all over at Professor Andrews&#8217; house, and there was like one junior in our class, I felt really sorry for that person &#8216;cause he was talking about, &#8220;Oh our time at Grinnell, our four years at Grinnell.&#8221; And he was my tutorial professor too; a couple of our tutorial professors.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>1090.18</start>
    <end>1119.01</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; So, it was just kind of a retrospective and then we were talking about how strange it had been and how it still affected us and, &#8216;cause we were still worried a little bit, every hell week, to see if anything would happen and fortunately nothing really like that ever did again. I mean, it was the only other time I remember talking about it.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>1119.02</start>
    <end>1123.18</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Do you feel like campus recovered from it?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>1123.19</start>
    <end>1163.15</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Yeah. I mean, by the time I graduated it was only us who remembered, so... And, I feel like we moved on, mostly, or at least we tried to forget about it. But it was still just sort of in the back of everybody&#8217;s mind, I think. It&#8217;s a big experience to go through your first year of college, on a small campus. We had some other people die but it wasn&#8217;t really, wasn&#8217;t really the same, fortunately.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>1163.16</start>
    <end>1209.07</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; But it&#8217;s a stressful place, and one of the attractions of Grinnell is that it's for all kinds of people who are quirky and really smart. The problem with people who are quirky and really smart is that sometimes they aren&#8217;t accepted by other people, other places and they&#8217;re not very happy all the time. They come here and, well, it&#8217;s in the middle of nowhere, and the weather&#8217;s really bad for a good chunk of the year. So, I don&#8217;t know. It&#8217;s a strange little place, this college. I mean, I love it, but I can see how it can be kind of a hothouse for unfortunate events.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs &amp; Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>1209.08</start>
    <end>1226.16</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; How do you feel like today&#8217;s students compare with students when you were a student? Do you feel like there&#8217;s a big difference in the student body?&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; I don&#8217;t know you guys.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Yeah, that's true.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; You&#8217;re probably more hipsters than we were.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Probably.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>1226.17</start>
    <end>1265.04</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; With your skinny jeans, yeah. All we wore to class were pajamas in my day. We knew how to self-govern ourselves. Just kidding, nah, I don&#8217;t really know anybody who&#8217;s here right now. You guys seem great. I&#8217;m sure you&#8217;ll go on to do great things. I imagine you&#8217;re pretty much the same as we were, possibly a little more wealthy &#8216;cause I know the cost of tuition keeps going up, and I've heard some people complain about how Grinnell students are just so rich and entitled these days, but Grinnell students were pretty rich and entitled in my day. Not so much me, but.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs &amp; Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>1265.05</start>
    <end>1302.13</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; But some people.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Some people. And, you kind of have to be entitled to hear about this place in the first place, because this is an upper-echelon kind of college. It&#8217;s not one that everybody goes around talking about. You&#8217;re not going to hear about it unless you are in the top percentiles intellectually.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; How do you feel like that influences, I mean, you said that Grinnell is kind of an upper-echelon kind of place, but do feel like that attitude influenced the student body?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>1302.14</start>
    <end>1339.22</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Are we snobby because go to Grinnell? Probably a little. I&#8217;m definitely proud of having gone to Grinnell, and the fact that nobody&#8217;s heard of it does give us a certain exclusivity. "Oh, it&#8217;s not mainstream, it&#8217;s Grinnell," which adds to our hipster vibe, I&#8217;m sure. I don&#8217;t think that this is necessarily a snobby place but it being out of the mainstream does, does make it seem that way. I don&#8217;t necessarily think that people here are snobby, but we sound snobby when we talk about it.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs &amp; Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>1339.23</start>
    <end>1345.26</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Yeah, just a little bit.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; "You haven&#8217;t heard of it. It&#8217;s very special."&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>1345.27</start>
    <end>1363.06</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; If you were writing a history, this is kind of a funny question, if you were writing a history of Grinnell College, what events, or not necessarily events, but just what would you include from your time here?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>1363.07</start>
    <end>1396.13</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; I feel like my time here wasn&#8217;t marked by anything that extraordinary, really. I mean, it wasn&#8217;t like we had protests and stopped graduation happening. I&#8217;d probably put in Darby being torn down. That&#8217;s part of it, just &#8216;cause it was historical, but I don&#8217;t know. It's just... for better or worse, a time when not that much extraordinary happened I think.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>1396.14</start>
    <end>1401.2</end>
    <transcript>
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Yeah, well, I don&#8217;t have anymore questions. Do you have anything else you want to add?&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker</speaker>
    <start>1401.21</start>
    <end>1448.25</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; I don't know. I like Grinnell. I miss Grinnell. Every now and again I&#8217;m like, &#8220;I wish I could go to class at Grinnell,&#8221; &#8216;cause I just graduated from grad school and the people in my classes were.... not... up to Grinnell standards and that&#8217;s really gonna make me sound snobby, but I feel like Grinnell prepared me really well to handle anything else academic that was thrown at me, ever, &#8216;cause I thought grad school was a cakewalk, compared to the coursework I had here. Even though, in my program we had classes one day a week and we were teaching four days a week so it was basically grad school plus a full time job.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker>Mary Parker &amp; Heather Riggs</speaker>
    <start>1448.26</start>
    <end>1472.16</end>
    <transcript>
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Socially, I don&#8217;t know how well Grinnell prepared me. We&#8217;re kind of awkward here. I presume that continues.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; Of course, definitely.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; But I feel like it also creates really strong bonds between people, and I really appreciate the network of people that I have from Grinnell.&lt;/span&gt;
Heather: &lt;span class='speaker_1'&gt; OK, great.&lt;/span&gt;
Mary: &lt;span class='speaker_2'&gt; Thanks.&lt;/span&gt;</transcript>
  </cue>
</cues>